ablecommerce.com 2018-07-16

# Privacy Policy

The policy of the Able Solutions Corporation (Corporation) is to respect the privacy of all web site visitors to the extent permitted by law. This online privacy statement is intended to inform you of the ways in which this web site collects information, the uses to which that information will be put, and the ways in which we will protect any information you choose to provide us. 

There are four types of information that this site may collect during your visit: network traffic logs, web visit logs, cookies, and information voluntarily provided by you. 

### Network Traffic Logs

In the course of ensuring network security and consistent service for all users, the Corporation employs software programs to do such things as monitor network traffic, identify unauthorized access or access to nonpublic information, detect computer viruses and other software that might damage Corporation computers or the network, and monitor and tune the performance of the Corporation network. In the course of such monitoring, these programs may detect such information as e-mail headers, addresses from network packets, and other information. Information from these activities is used only for the purpose of maintaining the security and performance of the Corporation's networks and computer systems. Personally identifiable information from these activities is not released to external parties without your consent unless required by law. 

### Web Visit Logs

Corporation web sites routinely collect and store information from online visitors to help manage those sites and improve service. This information includes the pages visited on the site, the date and time of the visit, the internet address (URL or IP address) of the referring site, the domain name and IP address from which the access occurred, the version of browser used, the capabilities of the browser, and search terms used on our search engines. This site makes no attempt to identify individual visitors from this information: any personally identifiable information is never released to external parties, unless required by law. 

### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information stored by your web browser on behalf of a web site and returned to the web site on request. This site may use cookies for two purposes: to carry data about your current session at the site from one web page to the next, and to identify you to the site between visits. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you may turn them off in your browser, or may set your browser to ask you before accepting a new cookie. Some pages may not function properly if the cookies are turned off. Unless otherwise notified on this site, we will not store data, other than for these two purposes, in cookies. Cookies remain on your computer, and accordingly we neither store cookies on our computers nor forward them to any external parties. Unless otherwise notified on this site, we do not use cookies to track your movement among different web sites and do not exchange cookies with other entities. 

### Information Voluntarily Provided by You

In the course of using this web site, you may choose to provide us with information to help us serve your needs. For example, you may send us electronic mail (through a mailer or a web form) to request information, you may sign up for a mailing list, or you may send us your address so we may send you an application or other material. Any personally identifiable information you send us will be used only for the purpose indicated. Requests for information will be directed to the appropriate staff to respond to the request, and may be recorded to help us update our site to better respond to similar requests. We will never sell, exchange or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information, except to the extent required by law. We do not retain the information longer than necessary for normal operations. Each web page requesting information discloses the purpose of that information. If you do not wish to have the information used in that manner, you are not required to provide it. Please contact the person listed on the specific page, or listed below, with questions or concerns on the use of personally identifiable information. 

### Trademarks and Service Marks

'AbleCommerce', 'CommerceBuilder', 'Software that Sells', 'Learn more... sell more' and 'Sell More' are registered trademarks or service marks of Able Solutions Corporation all rights reserved. All other trademarks, service marks, registered trademarks, or registered service marks mentioned in this website are the property of their respective owners. 

Corporation web sites provide links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. We do not control these sites and resources, do not endorse them, and are not responsible for their availability, content, or delivery of services. In particular, external sites are not bound by the Corporation's online privacy policy; they may have their own policies or none at all. Often you can tell you are leaving a Corporation web site by noting the URL of the destination site. 

If you have any questions about Able Solutions Corporation online security or privacy policies please let us know!
